Continuing Studies fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Non-credit programs, 1986 - 1999; F-94-4; 94 cm of textual records 11 photographs 2 contact sheets; Physical description: 11 photographs located in F-94-4-3-1-9
  - Management Skills in Advanced Technology (MSAT) program, 1986 - 1998; F-94-4-3; 46 cm of textual records 11 photographs 2 contact sheets
    - Implementing Management Concepts in Advanced Technology courses, 1987 - 1996; F-94-4-3-5; 4 cm of textual records
      - Strategic Planning and Marketing, 1996; F-94-4-3-5-15 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
    - Managing Creative Technically-Oriented People courses, 1987 - 1988; F-94-4-3-6
      - Managing Creative Technically-Oriented People, 1987 - 1988; F-94-4-3-6-1 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
    - Project Management courses, 1988 - 1996; F-94-4-3-7; 1 cm of textual records
      - Project Management, 1988 - 1989; F-94-4-3-7-1 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Project Management, 1990; F-94-4-3-7-2 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Project Management, 1993 - 1994; F-94-4-3-7-3 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Project Management, 1995; F-94-4-3-7-4 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - Project Management, 1996; F-94-4-3-7-5 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
    - MSAT II, 1993 - 1998; F-94-4-3-8; 1 cm of textual records
      - MSAT II - feasibility planning, 1993 - 1994; F-94-4-3-8-1 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - MSAT II - Product Management for Technology Market Leaders, 1998; F-94-4-3-8-2 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - MSAT II - Management of Intellectual Property, 1998; F-94-4-3-8-3 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
      - MSAT II - Strategic Human Resources Management, 1998; F-94-4-3-8-4 (Archival box - standard 94-38)
- Publications, 1970 - 2004; F-94-5; 62 cm of textual records
  Series consists of publications created by the Office of Continuing Studies and its predecessors. Printed materials include course calendars and posters; lecture notices; conference and workshop programs; and brochures for courses offered by Continuing Studies.
  The files are open with no restrictions.
  - Continuing Studies course calendars and posters, 1971 - 2001; F-94-5-1; 33 cm of textual records
    - Course calendars, 1971 - 1973; F-94-5-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 94-39)
    - Course calendars - special audit/non-credit, 1972 - 1982; F-94-5-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 94-39)
    - Course calendars, 1974 - 1975; F-94-5-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 94-39)
    - SFU/Kelowna program course calendars, 1975 - 1980; F-94-5-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 94-39)
    - SFU/Fraser Valley College program course calendars, 1975 - 1981; F-94-5-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 94-39)
    - Course calendars, 1976 - 1977; F-94-5-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 94-39)
    - Directed Independent Study Courses/Distance Education program, 1976 - 1979; F-94-5-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 94-39)
    - Course calendars, 1978 - 1979; F-94-5-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 94-39)
    - Course calendars, 1980 - 1981; F-94-5-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 94-40)
    - Courses - oversized posters, 1980 - 1981; F-94-5-1-0-10
    - SFU/Kelowna and Fraser Valley College programs - oversized posters, 1980 - 1981; F-94-5-1-0-11
    - Directed Independent Study Courses/Distance Education program, 1980 - 1984; F-94-5-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 94-40)
    - Directed Independent Study Courses - oversized posters, 1981 - 1982; F-94-5-1-0-13
    - Course calendars, 1982 - 1983; F-94-5-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 94-40)
    - Courses - oversized posters, 1982 - 1987; F-94-5-1-0-15
    - Extension Credit program calendars, 1983 - 1985; F-94-5-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 94-40)
    - Course calendars, 1984 - 1987; F-94-5-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 94-40)
    - Directed Independent Study Courses/Distance Education program, 1985 - 1999; F-94-5-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 94-40)
    - Extension Credit program calendars, 1986 - 1987; F-94-5-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 94-40)
    - Knowledge Network (Educational Telecommunications), 1986 - 1987; F-94-5-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 94-41)
    - Knowledge Network (Educational Telecommunications) - oversized posters, 1987; F-94-5-1-0-21
    - Extension Credit program calendars, 1988 - 1989; F-94-5-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 94-41)
    - Courses - oversized posters, 1988 - 1991; F-94-5-1-0-23
    - Extension Credit program calendars, 1990 - 1991; F-94-5-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 94-41)
    - Course calendars, 1990 - 2001; F-94-5-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 94-41)
    - Extension Credit program calendars, 1992 - 1993; F-94-5-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 94-41)
  - Lectures, workshops and conferences, 1970 - 2001; F-94-5-2; 7 cm of textual records
    - Continuing Studies - sponsored seminars, workshops and conferences, 1970 - 1977; F-94-5-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 94-41)
    - Continuing Studies - sponsored free lectures, 1977 - 2001; F-94-5-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 94-41)
    - Continuing Studies - sponsored seminars, workshops and conferences, 1978 - 1979; F-94-5-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 94-41)
    - Programs of Excellence lectures, 1978 - 1981; F-94-5-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 94-42)
    - Continuing Studies - sponsored seminars, workshops and conferences, 1980 - 1989; F-94-5-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 94-42)
    - Continuing Studies - sponsored seminars, workshops and conferences, 1990 - 1996; F-94-5-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 94-42)
  - Programs, 1975 - 2004; F-94-5-3; 22 cm of textual records
    - Seniors Program, 1975 - 2004; F-94-5-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 94-42)
    - Management Development Program for Women, 1976 - 1984; F-94-5-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 94-42)
    - Opera Studies Program/Arts Downtown, 1976 - 2003; F-94-5-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 94-42)
    - British Columbia Studies certificate program, 1977 - 1981; F-94-5-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 94-42)
    - Health and Fitness Studies Certificate Program, 1977 - 1983; F-94-5-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 94-42)
    - Applied Sciences Programs, 1977 - 2004; F-94-5-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 94-42)
    - Extended Studies Diploma Program, 1978 - 1982; F-94-5-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 94-42)
    - French Canadian Studies Certificate Program, 1980 - 1981; F-94-5-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 94-42)
    - Professional Development Programs, 1983; F-94-5-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 94-42)
    - Writing and Publishing Program, 1983 - 1989; F-94-5-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 94-42)
    - Liberal and Professional Studies Program, 1984 - 1985; F-94-5-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 94-42)
    - Liberal and Professional Studies Program - oversized posters, 1984 - 1985; F-94-5-3-0-12
    - Liberal and Professional Studies Program, 1985 - 2003; F-94-5-3-0-13 (Archival box - standard 94-42)
    - Canadian Centre for Studies in Publishing program, 1987 - 1997; F-94-5-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 94-43)
      Canadian Centre for Studies in Publishing; Textual records
    - Management for Non-Profit and Voluntary Sector Organizations Program, 1988 - 1989; F-94-5-3-0-15 (Archival box - standard 94-43)
    - Certificate Programs, 1988 - 1998; F-94-5-3-0-16 (Archival box - standard 94-43)
    - Advanced Interpreter Education Program, 1989; F-94-5-3-0-17 (Archival box - standard 94-43)
    - Writing and Publishing Program, 1990 - 1996; F-94-5-3-0-18 (Archival box - standard 94-43)
    - Foundation Program in Management for Women, 1991 - 1992; F-94-5-3-0-19 (Archival box - standard 94-43)
    - Arts and Cultural Administration Program, 1995; F-94-5-3-0-20 (Archival box - standard 94-43)
    - Opera Studies Program/Arts Downtown - oversized posters, 1996 - 2001; F-94-5-3-0-21
    - City Program, 1996 - 2004; F-94-5-3-0-22 (Archival box - standard 94-43)
    - Professional Designation Program, 1996 - 2004; F-94-5-3-0-23 (Archival box - standard 94-43)
    - Executive Travel Study Program, 1997 - 1998; F-94-5-3-0-24 (Archival box - standard 94-43)
    - Writing and Publishing Program, 1997 - 2004; F-94-5-3-0-25 (Archival box - standard 94-43)
    - Philosophers' Café, 1999 - 2003; F-94-5-3-0-26 (Archival box - standard 94-43)
    - English Language and Culture Program, 2000 - 2001; F-94-5-3-0-27 (Archival box - standard 94-43)
    - Urban Design Program, 2000 - 2004; F-94-5-3-0-28 (Archival box - standard 94-43)
    - Dialogue Program, 2004; F-94-5-3-0-29 (Archival box - standard 94-43)